<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>OutOfBounds | Praneet Shekhar</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on OutOfBounds | Praneet Shekhar</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.145.0</generator>
    <language>en-in</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 02:27:36 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Building This Site</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/building-this-site/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Sep 2023 02:27:36 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/building-this-site/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is a supposed to be simple site, a simple presence for me on the web.&lt;br&gt;
I needed a tool that makes things simple.&lt;br&gt;
While going through the portfolio of few of my seniors, I came across &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io&#34;&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Having mostly used Python &amp;amp; Flask for such purposes before, I needed something as simple but didn&amp;rsquo;t want to pull out a Swiss knife for buttering bread.
Hugo seemed to fit the bill perfectly.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>TCS IT Wiz 2016</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/tcs-it-wiz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Dec 2016 19:52:10 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/tcs-it-wiz/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The Kolkata edition of TCS IT Wiz 2016 was held on the 31st of August.&lt;br&gt;
It is a highly anticipated quiz and a marquee event in the quizzing calendar, being the biggest inter-school IT quiz.&lt;br&gt;
Our school has a rich history in this quiz, with our seniors winning several editions.&lt;br&gt;
So the pressure was immense, especially coming up against the reigning National Champions, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/adnan-azmat-496000153/&#34;&gt;Adnan Azmat&lt;/a&gt; &amp;amp; &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/shadankalam/&#34;&gt;Shadan Kalam&lt;/a&gt;, two incredibly knowledgeable and exceptional quizzers.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>COFAS 2016</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/cofas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Nov 2016 19:52:10 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/cofas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The 2016 edition of COFAS, the biennial international computer olympiad organised by City Montessori School, Lucknow was held in the month of November.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There were teams from several countries participating in a pleathora of competitions.&lt;br&gt;
Five of us represented Loyola School Jamshedpur in various events.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was part of the Computer Quiz and the Game Design Challenge.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.linkedin.com/in/anubhavkumar11/&#34;&gt;Anubhav Kumar Singh&lt;/a&gt; and I won the quiz in a dominating fashion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We stood 2nd in the Game Design Challenge where we created a gamified science learning platform.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi, I am Praneet Shekhar.&lt;br&gt;
I am from Jamshedpur - The Steel City of India. Also known as Tatanagar, after the Tatas who set up this city. &lt;br&gt;
I did my schooling from &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.loyolajsr.com&#34;&gt;Loyola School, Jamshedpur&lt;/a&gt; and my engineering in Information Technology from &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.kiit.ac.in&#34;&gt;Kalinga Institute of Industrial Technology, Bhubaneswar&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br&gt;
Currently based out of Mumbai, I work for Oracle Financial Services.&lt;br&gt;
My primary area of focus is data engineering.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am passionate about all things technology, especially the business of it.&lt;br&gt;
Apart from school curiculum, where we were introduced to programming with LOGO &amp;amp; GW-BASIC in early classes, I started teaching myself coding in 6th grade when I discovered web development through my sister&amp;rsquo;s books who was studying computer engineering at the time.&lt;br&gt;
I was hooked.&lt;br&gt;
I spent hours on end tweaking CSS properties and playing with jQuery. I soon taught myself the basics of PHP and built my first website, it was a static music library with an integrated music player.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
